

Alexander HELBOK

Innsbruck/Austria | +43 681 81780037 alexander.helbok@hotmail.com

OVERVIEW

I am 20 years old and have a big passion for how and why things work the way they do.

During my high school studies, I discovered my big interest for Physics, especially Astrophysics, which I am pursuing further during my university studies. Besides, my interests stretch from sports to music and all the way to repairing bicycles and solving a Rubik's cube in a matter of seconds.

EDUCATION

EXPERIENCE

Universität Innsbruck

2021 - to date

PHYSICS BACHELOR DEGREE

GRG1 STUBENBASTEI

2012 - 2020

SCIENTIFIC HIGH SCHOOL

TAHATAI COAST SCHOOL

Term 4, October - December 2015

PRIMARY SCHOOL, PAPAMOA, NEW ZEALAND

MUSIKSCHULE OTTAKRING
MUSIC SCHOOL/PIANO LESSONS

2011 - 2021

RADSTUDIO INNSBRUCK

July 2019

SUMMER JOB AS BIKE MECHANIC

STÄDTISCHE KINDERGÄRTEN WIEN

2020 - 2021

Serving 9 months of compulsory civil service

SKILLS

IT - Skills Experienced: LATEX | \bigwedge Unix | \bigotimes Mathematica

Beginner: Python | © C

LANGUAGES *Native:* Italian & German *Fluent:* English *Beginner:* French

HOBBIES Sport: Importation | I

Other: Speedcubing | 3D Printing | Some Card Magic

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Physics bronze medal at the 4th International Olympiad of Metropolises in Moscow
- Admission to "Österreichische Studienstiftung" (University Mentoring Program)
- Austrian record holder for the Square-1 cube and the Rubik's Clock